<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - PivotTheNet</title><link>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/posts/</link><description>All Posts | PivotTheNet</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 12:42:18 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Active Recon Resources</title><link>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/active-recon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 12:42:18 -0500</pubDate><author>revsh3ll</author><guid>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/active-recon/</guid><description>Active Reconnaissance To gather intelligence by actively engaging the target.
In the active reconnaissance phase, we&amp;rsquo;re planning our future phases, like exploitation, by actively collecting information on the target by enumeration, scanning, etc.
Few examples:
What targets were found and what ports are open?</description></item><item><title>Passive Recon Resources</title><link>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/passive-recon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 12:42:26 -0500</pubDate><author>revsh3ll</author><guid>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/passive-recon/</guid><description>Passive Reconnaissance To gather intelligence without actively engaging the target.
In the passive recon phase, we&amp;rsquo;re planning our future steps by passively collecting information on the target by fingerprinting, using OSINT, etc.
Few examples:
Any email formats found? What names can we find related to the target?</description></item><item><title>DC-3 of the DC Series</title><link>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/dc-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate><author>revsh3ll</author><guid>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/dc-3/</guid><description>I enjoyed DC-2&amp;rsquo;s Tom &amp;amp; Jerry theme! It showed us the concept of credential reuse and weak passwords, along with the misconfigurations of wordpress and SUID set binary.
Anyways, now onto DC-3.2 aka DC-3!
DC-3 Details Dropdown to see DC-3's quick overview DC-3 is another purposely built vulnerable lab with the intent of gaining experience in the world of penetration testing.</description></item><item><title>DC-2 of the DC Series</title><link>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/dc-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 12:30:00 -0500</pubDate><author>revsh3ll</author><guid>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/dc-2/</guid><description>With DC-1 out of the way, let&amp;rsquo;s move onto DC-2 of the DC Series!
DC-2 Details Click here to see DC-2's quick overview. Much like DC-1, DC-2 is another purposely built vulnerable lab for the purpose of gaining experience in the world of penetration testing.</description></item><item><title>DC-1 of the DC Series</title><link>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/dc-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 12:13:08 -0500</pubDate><author>revsh3ll</author><guid>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/dc-1/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s root DC-1!
Details can be found at https://www.five86.com/dc-1.html
Open this to see the box's overview pulled from the above website. DC-1 is a purposely built vulnerable lab for the purpose of gaining experience in the world of penetration testing. It was designed to be a challenge for beginners, but just how easy it is will depend on your skills and knowledge, and your ability to learn.</description></item><item><title>Networking Basics</title><link>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/networking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 12:40:34 -0500</pubDate><author>revsh3ll</author><guid>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/networking/</guid><description>Basics of Networking A network is two or more hosts connected together in order to exchange data. There&amp;rsquo;s two network types: WAN (Wide Area Network) - network that connects large geographical areas. LAN (Local Area Network) - network that is confined within a WAN network.</description></item><item><title>OSI Model</title><link>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/osi-model/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 12:40:27 -0500</pubDate><author>revsh3ll</author><guid>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/osi-model/</guid><description>OSI Layers &amp;amp; PDU OSI Model is a 7 abstract layer table that&amp;rsquo;s responsible for explaining the flow of data within a network. Experienced individuals will often call out an issue by the culprit layer number. example: &amp;ldquo;This is a level 3 issue.</description></item><item><title>Linux File Hierarchy</title><link>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/linuxfilehierarchy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 11:30:02 -0500</pubDate><author>revsh3ll</author><guid>https://PivotTheNet.GitHub.io/linuxfilehierarchy/</guid><description>/ Root - Where it begins Linux uses a tree oriented hierarchy, meaning it starts at one point and branches outward. This starting point is the / (system root) directory.
This particular hierarchy layout is based on the FHS (Filesystem Hierarchy Standard).</description></item></channel></rss>